Danielle Carvalho

Web and Mobile UI/UX Designer

Experience

Mogi Group (Remote)

Feb 2020 - Dec 2022

Senior Customer Service Representative

May 2021 - Dec 2022

- Make reports and searches.
- Identify spikes.
- Create Problem tickets.
- Escalate issues.
- Assist the support agents.
- Supervise the VIP support team, ensuring the quality of responses and ticket handling.
- Do onboarding process with new agents
- Provide Training

VIP Customer Service Representative

AUG 2020 - MAY 2021

• Handle VIP players tickets. (Technical tier 1 and purchases)

Customer Service Representative

FEB 2020 - AUG 2020

 Handle tickets. (Technical – tier 1 and purchases)



+1 (778) 636 5943

danielle fraga 23@gmail.com



്ന്ര /daniellefpcarvalho

About Me

Web and Mobile Development and Design student, at the age of 31 trying to change careers and conquer new knowledge. I have 9 years of customer service experience of which 7 years were spent in a child education school office and 2 years and 11 months as a customer service representative.

Skills

- Illustrator
- Photoshop
- In Design
- After Effects
- Figma
- Html & CSS
- UX Research

Social Media Manager (Brazil)

Jan 2020 - Jan 2021

Freelance

- Social Media Assets creation
- Copy
- Posts and Content Planning

Sistema de Ensino Recriar (Brazil)

Feb 2012 - Jan 2019

Administrative Assistant

- Customer Service
- Organize spreadsheets
- Fill out Admissions

Education

Langara College (Canada)

Sep 2023 - Dec 2024

Web and Mobile Development and Design

Federal University of Rio Grande Do Norte (Brazil)

Feb 2012 - Aug 2017

Social Communication and Advertising